Guide to the The Nick Zedd Papers 1963 - 2010 MSS.311
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Writing, 214733
  - Subseries A: Zedd A - Z, 214744
    - "Tempest" [Script Fragments with Notes, Cat Folder], c2002; 215035 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "Theory of Xenomorphosis" [Manuscript on Penetration Films Letterhead], undated; 215036 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "Theory of Xenomorphosis" for Bil Bok #10 [Magazine], 1999; 215037 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "Theory of Xenomorphosis" for Night #42 [Magazine], 1999; 215038 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "There Goes Your Neighborhood", May 13, 2002; 215039 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "They Eat Scum" [Treatment], 1978; 215040 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "They Eat Scum" [Script with Notes], c1978; 215041 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "Thimble of Oblivion" [Synopsis], 1983; 215042 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "The Threshold of Betrayal" for Play God Ink New Orleans [Manuscript and Zine], undated; 215047 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "Totem of the Depraved" [Manuscript], 1989; 215048 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - "Totem of the Depraved, Chapter Nine" for Scrawl Issue 4 [Magazine], 1997; 215049 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "The Transgressions of Cinema Bleed" for Headpress Number 5, 1992; 215050 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - "Tribute to Nick Bohn: (Censored by Hypocrisy Film Archives)", undated; 215051 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "Truce of Consequences," "Sacred Monster," [Blue Notebook, pages 1216 - 1356], 2001 - 2002; 215052 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "Truce of Consequences," "Sacred Monster" [Green Notebook, pages 1357 - 1573], 2001 - 2002; 215063 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - "Truce of Consequences," "Sacred Monster" [Coverless Notebook, pages 1574 - 1763], 2001 - 2002; 215064 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - "Truce of Consequences," "Sacred Monter" [Black Notebook, pages 1764 - 1959], 2001 - 2002; 215065 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Underground Film Bulletin #1 [Manuscript: Donna Death], 1984; 215066 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Underground Film Bulletin #2 [Manuscript: Lydia Lunch], 1985; 215067 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Underground Film Bulletin #3 [Manuscript: Pheobe Legere], 1985; 215068 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Underground Film Bulletin #4 [Manuscript: Richard Hell], 1985; 215069 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Underground Film Bulletin #5 [Manuscript: John Spacely], 1986; 215070 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Underground Film Bulletin #6 [Manuscript: Lung Leg], 1987; 215071 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Underground Film Bulletin #7 [Manuscript: Rockets Redglare], 1988; 215075 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Underground Film Bulletin #8 [Manuscript: Kembra Pfahler], 1989; 215072 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Underground Film Bulletin #9 [Manuscript: Casandra Stark], 1990; 215073 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Underground Film Bulletin [Fragments], undated; 215074 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - [Untitled Script], 1981; 215076 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - [Untitled Fragments], undated; 215077 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Project Description], undated; 215078 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - "War on Drugs: Saldo Drugs" for 11211 [Manuscript and Magazine], November 2004; 215079 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - "What is a Pre-Emptive Strike?" "No Future" for 11211 [Magazine], November 2002; 215080 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - "What is a Pre-Emptive Strike?" for ASS Magazine (Art Star Scene) [Magazine], 2003; 215081 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "What Would You Do If You Could Play God For One Day?" for Play God [Zine], undated; 215082 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - "Why I Hate Taboos", undated; 215083 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - "Why Was I Circumcised?" [Black Notebook], 1997; 215084 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch" [Transcription], c1983; 215085 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "Witchcraft Ban Letter", undated; 215086 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - "Your Neighborhood is Mine" for 11211 [Manuscript and Magazine], May 2002; 215087 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - "You've Got to be Kidding", undated; 215088 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - "Zedd Complains" [Hate Mail to Chris Gore], undated; 215089 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - "Zedd Responds" [Manuscript], undated; 215090 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - "Zedd Says" for Jicket Teen Magazine [Zine], undated; 215091 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Juvenelia, 214745
    - 25th Century Magazine #1 [Manuscript], January 1970; 215092 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - 25th Century Magazine #2 [Manuscript], April 1970; 215093 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - 25th Century Magazine #3 [Manuscript], July 1970; 215094 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 25th Century Magazine #3 [Photocopy with Color], July 1970; 215095 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - [American School of Osteopathy Notebook], 1911, 1977; 215096 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Doomsday #1 [Zine], December 6, 1977; 215097 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Doomsday #2 [Zine], 1978; 215098 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Doomsday Volume 3, Number 3 [Zine], Spring 1979; 215099 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - [Environmental Report], undated; 215100 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - "Explorers of Space" [Report], undated; 215101 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Harding Film Catalog [Manuscript], 1970; 215102 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Harding Film Catalog #2, 1970; 215103 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Harding Film Catalog #3 [Manuscript], c1971; 215104 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Harding Film Catalog #4 [Manuscript with Photographs], 1974; 215105 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - High Point High School Yearbook [Beltsville, Maryland], 1973; 215106 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - [High School and Collegiate Writing, Black and White Doodler Folder], c1973 - 1992; 215107 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Jim Harding's XINE (formerly 25th Century) 4th Issue [Black Ring Bound Sketchbook], November 1972; 215468 (Box 13, Box-folder 2)
    - Jon Harding's Plaspheria Portfolio Witty Story Volume 1, Number 2 [Manuscript], 1972; 215108 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - "Latium Americus" [Report with Green Binder], undated; 215109 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - "Juried: Senior Art Show Censored" for Prattler, c1977; 215110 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Prattler: Pratt Paper II, February 1977; 215111 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Prattler Volume 39, Number 9, March 16, 1977; 215112 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Prattler Censored Volume 1, Number 1, April 18, 1977; 215113 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Secret Agent Freddy and the Deadly Devices [Manuscript], 1966; 215114 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - [Sci-Fi Sketches], undated; 215115 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Sons of Demons Number 5 [Manuscript], February 1972; 215116 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Venusian Press #2 [Ring-Bound Sketchbook], December 1972; 215117 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Venusian Press [Fragments removed from XINE Sketchbook], 1971; 215118 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Subseries C: Source and Subject Files, 214746
    - [Albania], c1990; 215119 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - [Allin, GG], c1993; 215120 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - [Art], c1987 - 1999; 215121 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - [Brando, Marlon], c1994; 215122 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - [Business Cards, Paper Elements], c1994; 215123 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - [Comics], 1974 - 1990; 215124 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - [Film], various; 215125 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - [Hell, Richard], various; 215126 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - [Kern, Richard], various; 215127 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - [Literature], various; 215128 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - [Lunch, Lydia], various; 215129 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - [Music], various; 215130 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - [Pfahler, Kembra], 1990 - 1993; 215131 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - [Philosophy], various; 215132 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - [Politics], various; 215133 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - [Saint Reverend Jen], 2006 - 2009; 215134 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - [Sex], various; 215135 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - [Sex Pistols], various; 215136 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - [Smith, Jack], c2004; 215137 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - [Sprinkle, Annie], various; 215138 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - [Stark, Casandra], c1986; 215139 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - [Taste], various; 215140 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - [Waters, John], various; 215141 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - [Wood, Jr., Edward D.], various; 215142 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - [Wrestling], various; 215143 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Subseries D: Other Authors, 214747
    - "America the Fallen" by Robert Griffin, undated; 215144 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - "Countersunk Swivel Head: A Film Script" by Brian Carroll, undated; 215145 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - "Dogme 95: The Vow of Chastity", 1995; 215147 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - "Don't Call Me Rat-Dog!" by Reverend Jen Junior, undated; 215146 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - "Free for All" by Paddy Fitz, undated; 215152 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - "The Intruder (L'Intruse): A Play in One Act" by Maurice Maeterlinck, 1891; 215148 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - "Lydia Lunch Wrote This and Gave It to Me", undated; 215149 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - "Not Yield to Fear: Rough Treatment" by Klemann Films T.M., June 10, 1995; 215150 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - "Once Upon a Time" by Patrick McGoohan, undated; 215151 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - "Pay to Live" by Richard Klemann [copy 1], undated; 215153 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - "Pay to Live" by Richard Klemann [copy 2], undated; 215154 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - "Pitchblack: A Film Script" by Brian Carroll, undated; 215155 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - "Pizza Couple F (Solange Monnier, Green Revision with Notation)", April 12, 1995; 215156 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - [Poetry by Sue], undated; 215157 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - "The Prisoner: Dance of the Dead" by Anthony Skene, 1966; 215158 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - "The Randau" by Mark Doucet, March 1989; 215159 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - [Unidentified Script], undated; 215160 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - "Untitled Electra Elf Script" by Marc Slanger, undated; 215161 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - "Vampire's Kiss" by Lydia Lunch, c1989; 215162 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - "Warner Brothers" by Greg Ford, c1974; 215163 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - "Where Evil Dwells" by Tommy Turner and David Wojnarowicz [Script], 1985; 215164 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Series II: Projects, 214734
  Series II: Projects documents the production development of films involving Zedd and the publishing process of his written works. Elements are organized by document type and alphabetically by project title or subject, then chronologically.
  Subseries A: Development includes administrative and pre-production documents.
  Subseries B: Distribution contains post-production and distribution materials, including ephemera, flyers, posters and festival programs.
  Subseries C: Interviews preserves restrospective press about Zedd.
  Subseries D: Ads, Reviews and Literature includes ad spots, project press, and literature that includes discussion of Zedd's work and The Cinema of Transgression Movement.
  Subseries E: Other Artists and Events contains promotional material of events not featuring Zedd's work.
  - Subseries A: Development, 214748
    - The Academy of American Poets [Pamphlet], undated; 215165 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Administrative Materials], 2002 - 2005; 215166 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Administrative, Prop Lists, Notation], 2003 - 2006; 215167 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Administrative Materials], 2010 - 2011; 215168 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [BCAT Program Guide, Contracts], c2004 - 2007; 215169 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Episode List, Barcodes, Ivory Folder], 2005 - 2006; 215170 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Mock-ups for Uncompleted Feature Film by Paul Hocahan, Nick Zedd, and Rev Jen], 2009; 215171 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: The Price is Wrong" [Storyboard and Shot Sketchbook], undated; 215172 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Production Fan Letters], undated; 215173 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Production Schedules and Shot Lists], 2004 - 2010; 215174 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Storyboard Sketches and Shot Lists], undated; 215175 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Collective: Unconscious [Application Materials], January 25, 2000; 215176 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - "The Deprogramming" [Production Development Materials], c1981; 215177 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - "The Deprogramming' [Storyboard Sketches with Dialogue], 1981; 215178 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - [Directory], undated; 215179 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - "The Freak From Suckweasel Mountain/Geek Maggot Bingo" [Talent Consent Forms], 1979 - 1982; 215180 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - "The Freak From Suckweasel Mountain/Geek Maggot Bingo" [Storyboard Sketch with Schedule], 1982; 215181 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Hometown Video Festival [Application Materials], 2005; 215182 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Howl Festival Committees [Contact List], 2003; 215183 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - "Lucifer Luncheonette" [Yellow Production Notebook], undated; 215184 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - "A Movie; Ecstasy in Entropy: Equation of Resistance" [Shot List with Illustrations], undated; 215185 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - [Nick Zedd Resume, Filmography, Company Graphics], undated; 215186 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - "Nick Zedd Work File", various; 215187 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - [Talent Files], undated; 215188 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Subseries B: Distribution, 214749
    - "A Benefit for the Lost Films of Nick Zedd", various; 215189 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - "Abnormal: The Sinema of Nick Zedd" [Mock-Ups, Assorted Images], 2001; 215190 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [BCAT Guides], 2005 - 2007; 215191 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [MNN Program Guides], 2008, 2010; 215192 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - "Elf Panties: Magical Elf Panties, A Coloring Book", undated; 215193 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - "Elf Panties: Audio-Visual Fun with Reverend Jen" [Book Only], undated; 215194 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Rev Jen Calendar", 2000; 215195 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Saint Reverend Jen Calendar", 2002; 215196 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Reverend Jen Calendar", 2004; 215197 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Flyers], c2003; 215198 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Flyers], c2009; 215199 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - "An Ordeal with Nick Zedd" [Halliwalls, Buffalo NY], September - October 1985; 215200 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - [Anthology Film Archives Flyers and Programs], various; 215201 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Bleed [Hanuman Books Order Form, Flyers], undated; 215202 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - "The Bogus Man" [Flyers], c1980; 215203 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - "The Bogus Man," "Fingered" [Internacional Short Film Festival, Portugal], July 1999; 215204 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - [Cinema of Transgression Event Flyers], various; 215205 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - "Cinema of Transgression, Volume 1" [Video Graphics], undated; 215206 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - "The Cinema of Transgression and Other Movies, Curated by Nick Zedd" [Program List], 1995; 215207 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - "Cinema of Transgression" [Ann Arbor Film and Video Festival Program], July 10 - 23, 1989; 215208 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - "Cinema of Transgression" [Bar Europa Event Program, Amsterdam], 1986; 215209 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - "Cinema of Transgression" [Dark Nite Musick Series Flyers, Program], March 25 - 26, 1989; 215210 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - "Cinema of Transgression" [FilmProjekt Program], April 1986; 215211 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - "Cinema of Transgression" [Goteborg Film Festival Program, Sweden], January - February 1988; 215212 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - "Cinema of Transgression" [Komm Calendars, Germany], 1990; 215213 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - "Cinema of Transgression: Films of Nick Zedd" [27th Annual Olympia Film Festival Program], November 12 -20, 2010; 215214 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - "Cinema of Transgression" [Super 8 Festival Program, Germany], June 1989; 215215 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - "Cinema of Transgression" [Stella Program, Germany], October 1988; 215216 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - "Cinema of Transgression" [Underground Film Fest Program, Germany], 1987; 215217 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - "Cinematrocities of Nick Zedd" [Flyers], c1987; 215218 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - "Collective: Unconscious Presents Nick Zedd Movies" [Flyers], c2001; 215219 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - "Consume and Die" [Layout Graphics], undated; 215220 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Deathtripping [Tyneside Cinema Flyers], November 1995; 215221 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - "Destination X" [Flyers], 1976; 215222 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - [DJ Nick Zedd Flyer Materials], c1998; 215223 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy" [Flyer Materials], c1999; 215224 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - "Elf Panties: The Movie" [Flyers], 2001; 215225 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - "Elf Panties: The Movie" [San Francisco Independent Film Festival Program], January - February 2002; 215226 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - [Events Featuring Nick Zedd Flyers], various; 215227 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - "Extreme Cinema/Celluloid Chaos" [La Cinematheque de Toulouse Program and Flyer, France], April - May 2003; 215228 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - "Film/Video Arts: Artist Mentor Workshops: Nick Zedd" [Programs], 1998 - 1999; 215230 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - "Films of Nick Zedd" [Bijou Festival Flyers, Program], March - April 1997; 215229 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - "Films of Nick Zedd" [Strandgut Program, Germany], October 1988; 215231 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - "Fingered," "King of Sex" [Flyers], c1987; 215232 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - From Entropy to Ecstasy [Flyers], undated; 215233 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - "From Trash to Transgression" [Cornerhouse Program, UK], 1995 - 1996; 215234 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo" [DVD Covers Graphics], c1990, 2002 - 2004; 215235 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo" [Flyers], undated; 215236 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo" [Music Video Distributors Publicity], c2002; 215237 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo" [Press Pack with Photographs, Flyers], c1983; 215238 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - "Generation Z" [DVD Cover Graphics], c1995; 215239 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - "The Intruder" [Flyers], undated; 215240 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - "Invisible Cinema" [Flyers], c1986; 215241 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - "I Was a Quality of Life Violation" [Flyers], c2002; 215242 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - "I Survived Michael Shit/Screen Tests" [Flyer], c1998; 215243 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - "Kiss Me Goodbye" [Images], c1985; 215244 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - "Llik Your Idols: The Cinema of Transgression" [XFANZ L.A. Erotica Film Festival Program], 2007; 215245 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - "Lord of the Cockrings" [Flyers], c2001; 215246 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - "Lord of the Cockrings" [NY Underground Film Festival Program], March 2002; 215247 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - "Me Minus You" [Flyers], c1985; 215248 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Millennium Film Workshop [Flyers, Programs], 1993, 2001, 2007; 215249 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Museum of Modern Art [Flyers, Program], 1989, 1998 - 1999; 215250 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - New York Film Festival Downtown [Flyers, Program], 1988; 215251 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - NY Underground Film Festival [Program], March 1997; 215252 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - "NY Underground Nick Zedd" [Stuttgart Flyers, Germany], March 1990; 215253 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - [Nick Zedd Appreciation Society Materials], c1988; 215254 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - "Nick Zedd Retrospective 2000" [Flyers], 215255 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - "Nick Zedd Teaches the History of Transgression in Cinema" [Flyers], c2008; 215256 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - "Night of the Living Zedd / Zedd Isn't Dead" [Flyers], 1992, 2007; 215259 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "No Wave Cinema" [Whitney Museum of American Art Program], October 1996 - January 1997; 215260 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Penetration Films [Distribution Materials], various; 215261 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Penetration Films Inc., Nick Zedd.com [Invoices, Domain Documents], 2005 - 2008; 215262 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Penetration Films Video Catalog, 1996; 215263 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Peter Strickland's Bubblegum" [Flyers], c1995; 215264 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Police State" [Whitney Museum of American Art, New American Film and Video Series Program], 1996 - 1997; 215265 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - "Police State" [Flyers], various; 215266 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "Puss in Boots" [Illustration for Howl Festival], 2008; 215267 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - "School of Shame" [Flyers], c1985; 215268 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "Screen Tests" [5th Annual NY Underground Film Festival Program], March 1998; 215269 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - "Shadows in the City" [Flyers], 1990; 215270 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - "Sinema of Nick Zedd" [Flyers, Mock-Ups], 2007; 215271 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - "Strange Love" [7th Annual Chicago Underground Film Festival], August 2000; 215272 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - "They Eat Scum" [Anthology Film Archives Program], July - August 1999; 215273 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - "They Eat Scum" [Flyers, Mock-Ups], c1979; 215274 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - "They Eat Scum" [Howl! 1st Annual Festival of East Village Arts], 2004; 215275 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - "Thrust in Me" [Flyers], c1985; 215276 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra" [Flyers], c2001; 215277 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra" [8th Annual Chicago Underground Film Festival], August 2001; 215278 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "Tom Thumb in the Land of the Giants" [Collective: Unconscious Flyers], c1999; 215279 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Totem of the Depraved [Flyers], c1997; 215280 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - "Tour '90: Nick Zedd NY Underground Filmmaker" [Flyers], 1990; 215281 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - "Transgression" [The Cinema Project Program], September 1998; 215282 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - "Transgressional Sinema: Nick Zedd Retrospective" [Reel Roundtable Program], May 12, 2003; 215283 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - "Transgressive Cinema" [Kino Weekender Program], September 1997; 215284 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - "Trilogy of Teri" by Kembra Pfahler [Flyers], 1989; 215285 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Underground Film Bulletin [Order Forms], c1989; 215286 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - "U.S. Underground Filmmakers" [Kino im Komm Program, Germany], March 1990; 215287 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Flyers, Mock-Ups], various; 215288 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - "What About Me" by Rachel Amodeo [Press Pack with Photographs], 1992; 215289 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - "Whoregasm" [Flyers, Mock-Ups], c1988; 215290 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - "Why Do You Exist / Screen Tests" [Flyers, Mock-Ups], c1998; 215291 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - "Why Do You Exist / Screen Tests" [5th Annual Chicago Underground Film Festival Program], August 1998; 215292 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch" [Flyers], c1983 - 1986; 215293 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Subseries C: Interviews, 214750
    - "Cable TV Interview with Nick Zedd", 1989; 215294 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - "Centerfold: Filmmaker Nick Zedd and Performance Artist Sue Manson" by Annie Sprinkle for Taste of Latex Number 9 [Magazine], 1993; 215295 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - "The Cinematrocities of Nick Zedd" by Jordi Torrent for Film Threat Number 10 [Manuscript with Magazine], 1986; 215296 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - "The Films of Nick Zedd: An Oasis of Horror in a Desert of Boredom", undated; 215297 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - "He Eats Scum" by Simon Rucker for L Magazine [Magazine], April - May 2004; 215298 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - [Images of Nick Zedd], undated; 215299 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - "Interview for 20-Dollar Film School", 2002; 215300 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - "Interview of Transgression: Talking with Nick Zedd" by Michael McCarthy, August 8, 1997; 215301 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - "Interview with Nick Zedd" by Dennis Cooper and "Zedd Interview Addendum" by Richard Hell for CUZ Number 3 [Journal], 1989; 215302 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - "It's Hard to Maintain Your Sanity..." [Manuscript], undated; 215303 (Box 7, Folder 45)